Sunny
Yesterday my life was filled with rain
You smiled at me and really eased the pain
Sunny
The dark days are gone and the bright days are here
My sunny one shines so sincere
Sunny one so true
I love you
Sunny
Thank you for the sunshine bouquet
Thank you for the love you brought my way
Sunny
You gave to me your all and all
Now I feel ten feet tall
Sunny one so true
I love you
Sunny
Thank you for the truth you let me see
Thank you for the facts from
Sunny
A to
Z
My life was torn like a windblown sand
And the rock was formed when you held my hand
Sunny one so true
I love you
Sunny
Thank you for the smile upon your face
Thank you for the gleam that shows its grace
Sunny
You're my spark of nature's fire
You're my sweet complete desire
Sunny one so true
I love you